STETO JAVELLANA

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

 \sim

javellanasteto99@gmail.com

09275371519

Bacolod City, Negros Occidental,
Philippines

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An IT Professional with more than three (3) years and (2) months of experience in developing web applications. Highly instrumental in all phases of the SDLC, with expertise in algorithms and data structures. Can work in a fast-paced environment while maintaining attention to detail.



SKILLSET -

| Front-End | Back-End | Database | Others |
|----------------------------------|-------------------------|--------------------|-------------------------|
| Nuxt (3 years) | PHP / Laravel (3 years) | MySQL (3 years) | AWS Services (3 months) |
| Vuetify (3 years) | ASP.NET Core (1 year) | MSSQL (1 year) | Git (3 years) |
| Vue (3 years) | NodeJS (3months) | MongoDB (3 months) | GitHub |
| Vuex (3 years) | | | GitLab |
| JQuery (2 years and 2 months) | | | Postman |
| Bootstrap (2 years and 2 months) | | | |

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE -



2023 - Present

Spring Valley Tech Corp Bago City, Philippines

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

OOBRA

OOBRA is a digital jobs platform whose unique focus is the creation of digital agencies to further empower and develop digital workers. Accountability is at the heart of OOBRA's value proposition by allowing digital workers to focus on delivering worldclass services while the agencies leverage their competencies enhancing their attractiveness to the global clients.

Technologies: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Nuxt, Vue, Vuetify, PHP, Laravel, MySQL, POSTMAN, Git, Gitlab, REST Service

TELEHEALTH

A telehealth platform that lets patients and doctors conduct appointments remotely.

Technologies: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, JQuery, PHP, MySQL, Git, GitLab, SOAP Service

2022

Hanjen Technologies
Bacolod City, Philippines

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

HRIS AND PAYROLL

A cloud-based, multi-tenant HRIS and Payroll systems, this project aims to empower organizations to streamline HR operations, enhance decision-making capabilities, and drive efficiency across multiple entities. Through the seamless flow of real-time data, organizations can unlock new opportunities for innovation, collaboration, and growth in today's competitive business environment.

Technologies: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, JQuery, ASP.NET Core, MSSQL

2019 - 2020

Delcom Systems & Solutions Bacolod City, Philippines

PROGRAMMER STAFF

RECRUITMENT MANAGEMENT

The project entails the development and deployment of a customized In-House Recruitment Management System tailored to the organization's specific needs and objectives. By leveraging automation, integration, and data-driven insights, this initiative aims to revolutionize recruitment practices. This transformation enables organizations to streamline their recruitment processes, attract top talent, and gain a competitive edge in the talent market. Ultimately, it empowers organizations to build high-performing teams and efficiently achieve their business objectives.

Technologies: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Vue, Vuetify, PHP, Laravel, MySQL

PURCHASE REQUISITION

The process involves employees submitting a request through an online form and awaiting approval before purchasing any items or goods on behalf of the company.

Technologies: Html, CSS, JavaScript, Vue, Vuetify, PHP, Laravel, MySQL

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION SYSTEM

Bacolod City College